

STANISŁAW ZAJĄCZKOWSKI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

+48 504-563-386

staszek.zajaczkowski@gmail.com M

www.linkedin.com/in/s-zajaczkowski in

https://github.com/StaszekZ

www.staszek.ovh



I completed an intensive junior front-end developer course at infoShare Academy. Due to working under the supervision of the best Trainers I learned the latest frontend technologies and the use of good practices which I implement in my own projects. Simultaneously I am a research and teaching employee at the Medical University of Gdańsk, Poland. Managing research projects has taught me how to organize my work effectively.

EDUCATION = JUNIOR FRONT-END

DEVELOPER

infoShare Academy, Gdansk, Poland (02.2020 - 09.2020)

- bootcamp 240 hours Scrum,
- landing page: HTML, CSS, JS with BEM methodology
 - http://popeyeweather.jfdz14.is-academy.pl/
- weather app: HTML, CSS, JS, REST API and React and Redux
 - http://app.popeyeweather.jfdz14.is-academy.pl/

DOCTORATE DEGREE

MASTER DEGREE IN BIOLOGY

WORK EXPERIENCE

OWN PROJECTS

Medical University of Gdansk, Poland (11.2010 - 10.2016)

University of Gdansk, Poland (10.2003 - 07.2008)

A simple game built in pure JS using Google Firebase:

• https://infallible-brown-27d243.netlify.app/

Landing Page (HTML, CSS):

https://staszekz.github.io/landingPageOne/

React App for 'todos and notes' with Redux and Google Firebase

https://staszekz.github.io/notes.github.io/

Landing Page for Joanna Miklosz z with Bootstrap 4

https://www.joanna.science/

My own website

https://www.staszek.ovh/

RESEARCH AND TEACHING FMPI OYFF

Medical University of Gdansk, Poland (11.2014 - present)

- management of scientific projects,
- presentation of research results at international scientific conferences

SKILLS

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | REST API | React JS | Redux | GIT | NPM | VSCode | Bootstrap 4 | Webpack

METHODOLOGIES

SCRUM | BEM | Agile (jira)

LANGUAGE english-level C1

hereby authorize the processing of my personal data included in my job application for the needs of recruitment processes accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016 / 679 of 27.04.2018 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, as well as repealing Directive 95 / 46 / EC (Data Protection Directive). In addition, I authorize the processing of my personal data included in my job application for the needs of future recruitment processes.